[THUDS]
BOWERY KING: "I am the way
into the city of woe.
"I am the way into eternal pain.
[YELLING] "I am the way
to go among the lost.
"Before me, there were
no created things.
"But those that last forever.
"As do I!
"Abandon all hope you who
are about to enter here."
You are now in the presence
of the motherfuckin' king!
[LAUGHING]
You ready, John?
Yeah.
[SNICKERS]
MAN 1: Move! John Wick!
[MAN 1 SHOUTING IN ARABIC]
[MAN 1 EXCLAIMS IN ARABIC]
[MAN 1 SHOUTS IN ARABIC]
[MAN 1 SHOUTING IN ARABIC]
[MAN 1 GROANS]
[GUNFIRE IN DISTANCE]
[GUNSHOT]
[MAN 2 EXCLAIMS IN ARABIC]
[MAN 2 GROANS]
[MAN 3 YELLING IN DISTRESS]
[MAN 3 GROANS]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
Mr. Wick.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
My ring.
My freedom.
Your ring is gone,
like The Elder before me.
And if you came here thinking
you could end this
by killing me,
then you are mistaken.
My death will not
change the outcome
any more than you can
change your nature.
None of us
can escape who we are,
and no one escapes The Table.
And the only way John Wick
will ever have freedom
or peace, now or ever,
is in death.
I know.
I'm afraid you've come
a very long way
for nothing.
Yeah...
Not really.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SIREN WAILING]
[CAR ENGINE STOPS]
The Manager, please.
A Harbinger is here
to see you, sir.
WINSTON: This must
be a mistake.
HARBINGER:
There is no mistake.
By order of the Marquis,
Vincent Bisset de Gramont,
this hotel has been condemned.
[BRIEFCASE CLICKS]
[THUDS]
You have one hour.
[CLOSES BRIEFCASE]
He is expecting you.
Can they do this, sir?
The decree is signed
by the 12 members of The Table,
giving the Marquis
the power of autem imperator,
which means he is
now our judge, jury and...
[KNOCKS THE TABLE]
Evacuate the hotel.
WINSTON: Ned Kelly's final words
as the hangman slipped
the noose
around his neck were...
"Such is life."
Can you imagine the
acceptance, the defiance?
Today is not the day
you will die.
Of that, I am sure.
You have the unshakeable
faith of David, my friend,
but you shouldn't be here.
This will not be pleasant.
Such is life, sir.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
MARQUIS: [IN FRENCH ACCENT]
My father used to say,
"How you do anything
"is how you do everything."
Called it the first
and the last rule of life.
[SAND FALLING]
You believe in rules...
Mr. Manager?
Oh, I do.
MARQUIS: And what
of consequences?
Of course.
And second chances.
Ah. That's where we differ,
you and I.
[SAND FALLING]
Second chances
are the refuge of men who fail.
[STIRRING AUDIBLY]
[CLINKING]
Mm. [SMACKS LIPS]
There are those on The Table
who blame this, um,
atrocity on New York.
They believe it's this city.
The Table has indulged this
fucking place for too long.
And look where
that has gotten us.
I shot him.
[CHUCKLING] And yet he lives,
polluting everything he touches.
Marquis, respectfully,
my hotel...
MARQUIS: Your hotel?
If I might, sir?
By all means.
The Continentals
and their management
are a reminder
to all who sit beneath The Table
that none of us
are above the rules.
And yet we are here.
Sir, Mr. Wick...
We're not here
because of John Wick!
He is simply the face
of your failure, Mr. Manager.
The sand in that glass
is merely an echo
of my remaining patience.
[SAND WHISTLING]
[MUFFLED EXPLOSION]
You are no longer New York.
[KNUCKLES CRACKING]
You are nothing.
You are Excommunicado.
And as such...
you no longer need the
services of a concierge.
[GASPING]
It has been an honor,
my friend.
[BREATHING SLOWLY]
[BREATHING CEASES]
It should have been me.
MARQUIS: Yes.
But it wasn't.
Now, you think about
why that is,
and perhaps one of us will have
benefited from this conversation.
[IN FRENCH]
[PIANO TUNE PLAYING]
[PIANO TUNE PLAYING ON WATCH]
[PLAYING SAME TUNE]
[WHISTLES]
[MARQUIS TUT-TUTS]
I have a name for you.
[CHUCKLES] Respectfully,
I'm retired.
Finished. Done.
MARQUIS: I disagree.
CAINE: I'm no use to you.
Or The Table.
[CHUCKLING] That's not
for you to decide.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFLES]
I think you should
find someone else.
You came close.
Today.
Too close.
You put her in danger.
[SIGHS]
[TAPS CANE]
I know the deal I made.
A former associate, I believe.
He was.
And a friend.
Hmm.
The agreement with The
Table stays the same.
We give you a name,
you give us a life.
Or...
we take one.
[SNIFFS]
I will serve.
I will be of service.
[TAPS CANE]
Excellent!
I assume you have a notion
of where he might be?
John Wick has few friends
remaining in the world,
and even fewer he trusts
with his life.
MARQUIS: Very, very good.
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING]
[PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Welcome to the Osaka Continental.
How can I help?
Yeah, I'm lookin' for a room.
I'm afraid this facility
doesn't allow animals.
Emotional support animal.
She's your support animal?
Other way round.
I'm hers.
Isn't that right?
She stays in your room.
Enjoy your stay, sir.
It's not too bad.
Not bad at all.
[MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD]
There is a dog in my lobby.
[SIGHS]
Emotional support animal.
Of course it is.
Tomorrow's schedule.
Mr. Suzuki at 11:00
and the Tarasovs are
requesting an audience at 2:00.
What's this at 8:00?
Dinner with your daughter.
She says she's
concerned you've been
working too hard.
What must I have done to deserve
such a considerate child?
Good karma,
I suppose. Indeed.
And how are our guests?
[SIGHS] Some of our gold
club members are anxious.
It's always something.
And today it's New York.
And my concierge?
Concerned.
Perhaps we should get you
an emotional support animal.
[DRUMS BEATING]
[CONCIERGE SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
MAN: We've done nothing
to offend The Table.
CONCIERGE: [IN ENGLISH] Your
relationship with Mr. Wick is no secret.
The Table will come.
[ARROW WHIZZES BY]
[ARCHER APOLOGIZES IN
JAPANESE] MAN: And...
will be met
with our grace.
Everything he touches dies.
[IN JAPANESE]
Forgive me, Father.
Akira.
[IN ENGLISH]
Please tell my daughter
that I look forward
to our dinner.
[ELECTRONIC RAP MUSIC PLAYING]
[FIRE ROARING]
[GLASSES CLINKING]
[IN JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
Apparently not.
Killing the Elder
was a mistake, my friend.
Their response was the destruction
of the New York Continental.
My daughter fears we are next.
Winston?
Alive, but they executed
his concierge
to prove a point.
Have you given any thought to
where this ends?
The Table will never stop.
You know this.
It only takes life
and only gives death.
Koji...
[IN JAPANESE]
Friendship means little
when it's convenient.
[WOMAN SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY
IN JAPANESE]
Welcome to the Osaka Continental.
How can I help?
The manager.
Por favor.
Of course.
Please, make
yourself comfortable.
[WHISPERS IN JAPANESE]
The only path
this leads to is death.
I'm going to kill them all.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I believe you'll try.
But no one,
not even you, can kill everyone.
You want to die?
That's your choice.
A good death
only comes after a good life.
You and I left
a good life behind
a long time ago, my friend.
Father, The High Table.
What is he doing here?
Mr. Wick
is our guest.
Father...
I'll talk to them. They
don't know you're here.
[IN JAPANESE]
Stay with Mr. Wick.
HENCHMEN: Hai.
[WOMAN ANNOUNCING
IN JAPANESE OVER PA]
[IN ENGLISH] Welcome
to the Osaka Continental, gentlemen.
How may I be of service?
The Table has reason to believe
that this facility
is providing services...
[IN LATIN]
That is a grave accusation.
We will require full
access to your hotel.
Of course.
But as you are well aware,
no business,
not even your kind of business,
may be conducted
on Continental grounds.
So, I'm going to have to ask you
to surrender your firearms.
We speak for the Marquis.
And I speak for Osaka.
Your guns,
please.
Don't repeat the mistake
that fool in New York made.
Fools talk, cowards are silent,
but wise men listen.
CAINE: So which one
will you be?
Hello, old friend.
[SIGHS]
So good of you to visit
after all these years.
You are with them now? No.
No.
Your daughter?
Mia?
Alive.
And your daughter Akira?
Well.
I'm glad.
You know...
we don't have
to end this with blood.
Then leave.
No one defies The Table.
I remember once
you understood that.
And I remember a time
when you understood
the meaning of brotherhood.
Enough!
By order of
the Marquis de Gramont,
this hotel has
been deconsecrated.
Step aside.
[SNAPS]
[LIGHTS SHUT DOWN]
Don't do this, Koji.
I'm sorry.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
[SHOUTS IN JAPANESE]
[IN SPANISH]
[WOMAN GRUNTING]
[IN ENGLISH] Get out.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
[IN JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Secure the hotel.
Find Wick.
[IN JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH]
If they find you here,
The Table will
kill my father, me,
everyone, because
you broke the rules.
You shouldn't have come.
[IN JAPANESE]
You armed?
[GUNSHOT]
[MAN GROANS]
[AKIRA GRUNTS]
[IN JAPANESE]
Hai.
[MUTTERS AFFIRMATIVELY]
[SLURPING]
[SPITS]
Hey!
[IN ENGLISH] Blind man!
[SLURPING]
Do your job!
[EXHALES]
[ARROW WHIZZES]
[TAPS CANE SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
[BOW CREAKS]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[BELL DINGS]
[MAN GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[BELL DINGS]
[YELLS]
[MAN GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
[GUNSHOT RICOCHETS]
[MAN SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[MAN CHOKING]
[GUNFIRE]
KOJI: Akira!
[IN JAPANESE]
[GRUNTS]
[AKIRA GROANS]
[IN ENGLISH] Get out
the way you came.
Go to the Umeda Station.
I'll stay.
Don't insult my gift to you.
And, John, do me
a small courtesy.
[IN JAPANESE]
[ASSENTS IN JAPANESE]
[GUN CLICKS]
[MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[GRUNTING]
[MAN SCREAMS]
[MAN GROANING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN SHOUTS IN DISTANCE]
[GUN CLICKS] [MAN 1
GRUNTS IN SURPRISE]
[GROANS]
[MACHINE GUN FIRES]
[GROANING]
[GUN CLICKING]
[SCREAMS]
[MAN SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[TAPS CANE]
[SCRAPING]
[CLINKS]
John?
Caine.
They gave you my name.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Me, too.
[GUNSHOTS]
[TAPS CANE]
CAINE: You should have
stayed out.
For all our sakes.
I tried.
[TAPS CANE]
Did you?
[TAP]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
Come on, John.
Let's get this shit over with.
[COCKS GUN]
Yeah. [PANTING]
That sounds like a good idea.
[GUN CLACKING]
[GUN MAGAZINE CLATTERS]
[TAPS CANE]
You took a deal.
Same as you, John.
Family?
[SIGHS]
Family.
[CLATTERS]
You dead, John?
[BREATHING QUIETLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GLASS CRACKS]
[GUN CLICKS]
[JOHN GRUNTING]
John.
Caine.
[GUNSHOT]
[GUN COCKS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE CLICKS]
[PHONE RINGS IN DISTANCE]
John Wick, open...
[CONTINUES IN JAPANESE]
John Wick...
[CONTINUES IN FRENCH]
[WOMEN SPEAKING
MULTIPLE LANGUAGES]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[JOHN PANTING]
[GUN COCKS]
[DOG GROWLS]
[YELPS]
[GUNSHOT]
[MAN CHOKING]
[DOG GROWLING]
Damn, Johnny.
This is quite the
mess you've made.
I don't know you.
But I know you.
[DOG GROWLING]
You a tracker?
How much?
Not enough.
But it's gettin' there.
I need you to take better
care of yourself, Johnny.
'Cause we're
in this together now.
[DOG SNARLING]
[AKIRA GROANS]
[AKIRA GASPS]
[AKIRA GASPING]
CAINE: All right, Koji.
Just tell me where John is
and get out of here.
Leave.
Go somewhere far away.
You know I won't.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[KOJI GROANS]
[IN JAPANESE]
[GROANS]
[SCRAPING]
You owe John Wick nothing.
He has no marker on you.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
KOJI: You must have
fallen far to believe
the only debts we have...
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
lie in markers.
Come on.
I don't want to do this.
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
[BLADE SLICES]
[GROANS]
Father!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Look at me.
Even a blind man knows
you have lost.
[SCOFFS]
And, Caine,
you don't need eyes
to see the right path.
Just take care of your daughter.
I...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I am.
[GRUNTS]
[KOJI GROANS]
No!
[GASPING]
[WHIMPERING]
CAINE: Don't.
Live.
[SWORD CLATTERS]
[AKIRA WHIMPERS]
I'll be waiting for you.
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[WOMAN ANNOUNCING
IN JAPANESE ON PA]
[BELL CHIMES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[WHIMPERS]
[TRAIN ACCELERATES]
Who is he?
He was a friend.
My father is dead
because of you.
Because of what you did.
So either you kill him...
or I will.
I understand.
[EXHALES]
[SIGHS]
[ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA]
Goodbye, Mr. Wick.
[BELL DINGS]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Thanks for coming.
Well, us homeless folk
do have to
stick together now, don't we?
I need to speak to him.
Last time you spoke to him,
you shot him off a roof.
I had no choice.
They held all the cards.
No.
But who held the gun?
John needs to know the breadth
of what's coming at him.
This Marquis is unrestrained.
The Table have
let him off the leash.
Oh, my dear Winston,
your benevolence is touching!
But tell me.
Tell me true.
Why did the Frenchman
let you live?
Killing a man can turn
him into a martyr.
Letting him live...
tells the world he's a
coward or a turncoat.
So what are you?
Aggrieved.
[OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[HORSES NEIGHING]
[SWORDS CLASHING]
I fail to see how laying
waste to Continentals
is getting you closer
to killing John Wick.
MARQUIS: This campaign
is not to kill John Wick.
It is to kill the
idea of John Wick.
And to do that, I must
destroy everything
that idea touches.
[SWORDS CLASHING]
The bloodshed in Osaka
was not necessary.
The bloodshed was the point.
He'll make it your choice.
You, come with me.
Think twice before accepting.
[HORSE WHINNIES]
And you are?
TRACKER: Nobody.
Coyness, Mr. Nobody,
is a pathetic trait.
A miscalculation,
in which by trying
to hide our ego,
we let it appear stark naked.
I will ask only once.
How were you able to locate him?
Pay and I'll tell you.
How much would such
a service be worth?
Twenty-five million,
plus a matching contribution
to my 401k
when he's dead.
Hmm.
We found him once.
We'll find him again.
Is that before
or after he puts you
in the ground?
I like you.
Twenty million.
Like me some more.
Twenty-three.
Ego, Mr. Nobody. Mm.
It's 23.
You clearly can afford it.
For the service.
Mm-hmm.
[SCREAMS]
[DOG BARKS]
TRACKER: Fuck!
[CONTINUES BARKING]
No, no, no.
No. It's okay.
Hey, it's okay.
Sit. Sit.
[GROANING]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
What the fuck is this, man?
A choice.
You can pull the knife out
or you can pull your hand out.
One shows me a man
committed only to himself,
and the other,
a man committed to the cause.
Which one are you?
[WHIMPERING SOFTLY]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[FLESH SQUELCHING]
[GROANING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[TRACKER GROANS]
[IN FRENCH]
Winston.
Jonathan.
My condolences.
He was a good man.
Yes, he was.
Taken for our sins.
Who is this?
The Marquis de Gramont.
Elevated only by his
guarantee of killing you.
All the resources of The
Table are at his disposal.
Where do I find him?
Paris.
Where will it end?
Huh?
With him dead.
Oh. And then?
Hmm?
Have you learned nothing?
They will replace him
before the body's cold.
Hercules had his Hydra.
You have The Table, except
you'll run out of bullets
before they run out of heads.
Kill him, but do it
the smart way.
And get him to give you
your freedom.
How?
Turn his rules and
consequences against him.
Challenge him to single combat.
High Table duels are a myth.
Wrong!
They're a cold hard fact,
and part of the foundation
of The Table
to stop its more combustible
members from outright war.
It's also, win or lose,
what you say you want,
a way out.
I don't sit at The Table.
Your family does.
Get them to issue the challenge
and then offer you up as proxy.
I don't have a family.
The Ruska Roma tore my ticket.
Then I suggest you
get your ass to Berlin
and get it mended.
Or...
pick a plot.
What do you get
out of this, Winston?
What you were so good
at getting, Jonathan.
Revenge.
[SLOW ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[IN RUSSIAN]
Hmm.
[PRIEST PREACHING IN RUSSIAN]
[JOHN GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[IN ENGLISH]
Nice suit.
[OPERATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
MARQUIS: Speak.
He's in Berlin,
at the Ruska Roma.
You can wire
that finder's fee now.
No.
Excuse me?
Kill John and you'll
get your money.
That wasn't part of our deal.
The deal was for your service.
And it's now a life
for a life, Mr. Nobody.
Yours or his.
When it's done,
you will have your prize.
And your pension.
[SIGHS]
Asshole.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[JOHN GROANS]
Jonathan Wick?
[GROANS]
[ROPE STRETCHING]
[IN ENGLISH]
You are forgetting
we are still under The Table.
And last I checked...
[CRANKING]
you are Excommunicado
and your ticket was torn.
You have no business with us.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH] Pyotr is dead!
After you
put a bullet
in The Elder's head,
the Marquis had one
put in Pyotr's.
And in fine Russian tradition...
[CHUCKLES]
He sent us the bill.
Because of you,
I had to kneel
in front of the man
who murdered my father.
[IN ENGLISH]
Then we have
a common enemy.
We can help each other.
[CHUCKLES] You can't
even help yourself.
How the hell are you
going to help us?
By killing this Marquis.
They just appoint another.
[IN RUSSIAN]
[CHOKES] It does
if I kill him in a duel!
[JOHN CHOKING]
[IN RUSSIAN]
[IN ENGLISH]
How many did you kill
to get out?
[STRAINING] A lot.
You will only have to kill one
to get back in.
The bastard who
murdered my father.
Give me the name.
Killa Harkan.
You will find him
at Himmel and Hölle.
When he's dead,
I will mend your ticket.
And the Crest?
[TUT-TUTS]
Harkan first, then we talk.
Bring proof of death.
[GRUNTS]
I'll need a way in.
KATIA: I know a way.
[CHUCKLES]
Klaus will take you.
I am Klaus.
[GRUNTS]
John.
I am Klaus.
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING]
Please tell your mistress
that I am honored
by this gesture
and I look forward to
our continuing partnership.
I am Klaus.
Mr. John Wick
in the flesh.
[CHUCKLES]
The Baba Yaga. [LAUGHS]
Must be Christmas, ja?
[LAUGHS]
[COUGHS]
[INHALES]
[EXHALES]
Where are
my manners? Please.
[BLADE SLICES]
A drink, Mr. Wick?
You were expecting me.
Not me.
Him.
CAINE: John?
[TAPPING CANE]
How are you?
You knew I'd be here.
I suspected it.
Family.
KILLA: That family
sold you out, Mr. Wick.
They gave you up
in the vain hope
of saving themselves.
You see, that's why
I never trust the Cossacks.
They are dirty people.
[SNICKERS]
This is personal.
I sense tension here.
Mr. Wick may
probably feel
I'm responsible
for the death of a...
mutual friend.
But I didn't kill Koji.
You did, John.
KILLA: You know, this
discord between old friends,
it saddens me.
Allow me to help.
Nein.
We have a deal.
Had.
The Marquis.
Hell, I doubt he'll
mind if it's bullets,
blades or a blind man.
[THUD]
[CHUCKLES LIGHTLY]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[IN GERMAN]
[IN ENGLISH] Is
this for me, Mr...
Nobody.
And, no, it's actually for him.
[KILLA LAUGHS]
Then take a seat, Mr. Nobody.
[LAUGHS]
Exciting, ja? [LAUGHS]
[KILLA CONTINUES LAUGHING]
[KILLA COUGHING]
[GROWLING]
So, you want to kill him.
You want to kill him.
I want to kill him.
What about
you, Mr. Wick?
I'm going to kill you.
[KILLA CHUCKLING] Oh.
For Pyotr. Of course, ja.
But it looks like
we have ourselves, uh,
a genuine conundrum. [CHUCKLES]
A quandary, if you will.
A real-life dilemma.
[CHUCKLES]
[KILLA CONTINUES] So...
How about we play a game?
One hand.
The winner decides who lives...
and who does not.
[KILLA CHUCKLING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
All right.
What's the buy-in?
More than you can afford.
[SCOFFS] Yeah,
I'm one bullet away
from being a very rich man.
Or a dead one.
Five-card draw.
Mr. Wick.
KILLA: Mr. Wick?
Dead man's hand, Mr. Wick.
Well...
I don't gamble.
Let's see.
Four nines. And a four.
Most impressive. [CHUCKLES]
KILLA: Ah. Royal flush.
Pretty good for a nobody.
Thank you.
A blind man, a guy with a dog
and John Wick walk into a bar
and take a seat at the table.
That either sounds
like the beginning
of a stupendous joke
or a most
profitable opportunity.
[CHUCKLES]
One thinks he can
serve his way out.
One...
thinks he can buy his way out.
And one...
thinks he can kill
his way out.
Each of them all think that
they have the winning hand.
But what they fail
to realize
is that the moment they took
a seat at The Table...
they had already lost.
Let me guess.
Five of a kind?
TRACKER AND JOHN: Yeah.
[IN CANTONESE]
KILLA: Just so you know,
Pyotr wasn't personal.
Now, maybe a little bit.
[KILLA YELPS]
[HENCHMAN GRUNTS]
Kill!
[BARKING]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[DOG GROWLING]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
[PIN CLICKS]
[GRENADE CLANKS]
[MEN SCREAM]
[IN CANTONESE]
[ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTING AND PANTING]
[IN ENGLISH] Hey!
He's over there!
[GRUNTING]
[ELECTRONIC DANCE MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[INHALES]
[IN GERMAN]
[GRUNTING]
[CHOKING]
[ROARS]
[THUDS]
[MUFFLED DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[INAUDIBLE] [MUSIC
INTENSIFIES IN VOLUME]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[HENCHMEN GROANING]
Nuts!
[BARKING]
[SCREAMING]
[DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KILLA GRUNTS]
Know what your
problem is, Mr. Wick?
You are unlucky.
Unlucky in life,
in love,
in friendship...
and now...
in death.
[LAUGHS]
[FLESH SQUELCHING]
[SCREAMS]
[DISTORTED GRUNTING]
[BLOWS THUDDING]
[DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
HENCHMAN: Killa!
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
[SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[INHALES]
[KILLA YELLS]
[KILLA GRUNTING]
[KILLA GROANS]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[PANTING HEAVILY]
Why don't you just die?
[SCREAMS]
[BONES CRACK]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[JOHN GRUNTING]
[CLAMORING]
CAINE: He's mine.
I told you not to take a deal.
Yeah, I guess your deal
didn't work out either, huh?
Huh?
Hell of a thing for them
to take your eyes, though.
They didn't take them.
I gave them.
[KATIA IN RUSSIAN]
[IN RUSSIAN]
[GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BOTH BREATHE HEAVILY]
[EXHALES]
[KATIA CHUCKLES]
[IN ENGLISH] The Ruska
Roma will support
your challenge.
Who will be your Second?
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
WINSTON: A warning
of the cost of tyranny.
MARQUIS: You must intend
to join your concierge.
WINSTON: Not today.
Per the Old Ways
and the old laws,
John Wick calls you to a duel.
To settle your differences
the old-fashioned way,
as gentlemen should.
You speak of the Old Ways
as if you know them.
A man of Mr. Wick's
station
cannot issue such a challenge.
He has his family's crest.
MARQUIS: Hmm.
Berlin.
Ruska Roma challenge,
the acceptance of Mr. Wick
back into the fold,
it's all there.
Recorded history now.
And why would I accept this
from a second-rate seat?
Because there are rules,
and without them...
We live with
the animals. Exactly.
MARQUIS: Mm.
Times are changing.
A new day is dawning.
New ideas, new rules,
new management.
Yet you will accept.
Because we all still sit
beneath The Table.
Even you are not immune
to the consequences of failure.
And what exactly
are Mr. Wick's terms?
Victoriae fiducia.
The unconditional release of any
and all obligations to The Table.
Ah, history is littered
with Marquis
who were only remembered
by their servants.
But you...
you could be remembered
as the man who brought
John Wick,
the most feared of all
by The Table and all who
sit at it, into the light.
Your light.
And who could predict
how high that kind of glory
could take a man in our world?
Noon, La Tour Eiffel,
to discuss rules.
You may go.
When I'm done.
As his Second, upon his victory,
my Excommunicado is to be
lifted, my title restored,
my hotel rebuilt
and re-consecrated,
all at The Table's expense.
Of course.
[IN FRENCH]
How you do anything
is how you do everything.
Now I'm done.
I think I'll miss you
when you're gone.
Shame I can't say the same.
You don't know, do you?
What's that?
A man's Second,
like his sponsor,
either walks out
with his champion
or is buried beside him.
The Old Ways.
Such is life.
[BELL TOLLING]
HARBINGER: Under the Old Laws,
only one can survive.
Do you both understand that?
[CONTINUES] Very good.
Rules.
The Challenged
chooses first. Time?
Sunrise.
Now.
HARBINGER: Sunrise.
Location?
You come here
thinking there is a way out of
this world for you, Mr. Wick?
There is not.
Le Centre Pompidou.
Sacré Coeur.
Weapons?
If you win,
The Table will honor its word.
You will have your freedom.
But you won't take it.
Blades.
Pistols.
HARBINGER: Dueling pistols.
Thirty paces.
In the event that
both parties survive,
each will approach the other
at increments of ten paces
until only one remains.
Rules of engagement.
No quarter.
MARQUIS: You know why you
won't take your freedom?
Hmm?
Because this is who you are,
who you've always been.
You are a killer.
An orphan we plucked
from the street
and honed into a knife.
And it is the killing
that gives you purpose.
A man without purpose...
is nothing.
No quarter.
HARBINGER: No quarter.
If there is nothing else, gentlemen,
I will see...
A nomination.
It is his right.
HARBINGER:
Do you have a name?
Caine.
HARBINGER: So be it.
Sunrise, Sacré Coeur.
Dueling pistols, no quarter.
Should Mr. Wick
be victorious,
he will be free of any
and all obligation
to The High Table,
and his Second
will be reinstated
as the manager of the rebuilt
New York Continental.
Should the Marquis Vincent Bisset
de Gramont be victorious...
John Wick will be dead.
As will his Second.
HARBINGER: Just so.
Now, if there is
nothing more, gentlemen,
I will see you at sunrise.
Failure to meet
at the appointed hour
will result in forfeiture
and immediate execution.
There is no John out there.
No happy husband
with a normal life.
There's only John Wick,
the killer.
And he's going to kill you.
[TAPS CANE]
JOHN: Your hotel?
Yes.
You always have
an angle, don't you?
Doesn't everyone?
Let's find safe harbor
before it starts.
There's something
I need to do first.
Sooner rather than later.
Won't do it.
You fight your own fight.
Isn't this what you want?
Hmm?
Victoriae fiducia.
You kill him,
and you and your
daughter will be free.
No one can touch her.
If you don't,
she will have to face
the consequences.
The choice is yours.
Caine.
John.
Saying goodbyes?
Saying hello.
You think your wife
can hear you?
No.
Then why bother?
Maybe I'm wrong.
The dead are gone.
Only the living matter.
After my daughter was born...
I wanted to leave this life.
[TUNE PLAYING ON WATCH]
I thought I did.
But you didn't.
We're damned...
you and I.
On that we agree.
[MUSIC STOPS]
My daughter's not.
If it's between you and her...
you're going to die.
Maybe not.
I missed you, John.
It's so good
to sit with a friend.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[WATER SPLASHING]
This is how you
resolve the situation?
Duello with the Baba Yaga.
Failure will shake the
foundation of The High Table,
and it will turn Wick
into a saint.
My victory will do the opposite.
[HARBINGER SCOFFS]
Marquis de Gramont!
A man's ambition
should never exceed his worth.
You would do well
to remember that, sir.
[SENTIMENTAL
FRENCH SONG PLAYING]
[MUFFLED FRENCH SONG
CONTINUES PLAYING ON RADIO]
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
Bonjour, Monsieur Wick.
And welcome to La Resistance.
A little far from home,
aren't you?
Well, your little act
of uncivil disobedience
inspired me, John.
I'm branching out,
spreading my wings.
How goes the Grand
Farewell Tour?
Coming to an end.
So it seems. So it seems.
Forty-two regular, wasn't it?
It's Kevlar, front to back.
The latest in ballistic chic.
Appropriate for
all formal occasions.
Weddings, funerals,
High Table duels.
After all, a man
has to look his best
when it's time to get married.
Or buried.
Forgive me, sir,
but this is madness.
Madness?
Trusting your fate
to a blind man?
There are three types
of men in this world.
Those who have
something to live for,
those who have
something to die for,
and those who have
something to kill for.
John Wick has
none of these things.
He is but a ghost
in search of a graveyard.
But the blind man,
well, he has all three.
Besides, I have a feeling
Mr. Wick will never make it
to the duel by sunrise.
[IN SPANISH]
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
All right, now.
For all you boppers out there
in the City of Lights,
for all you street people
with an ear for the action,
to all my loyal listeners
who know the beat of the street...
[TURNS UP RADIO]
tonight is your chance
to make some beautiful music.
I've been asked
to relay a special request
from a secret admirer.
It seems there's a thorn
in our little slice of paradise.
A wicked man from the Big Apple
is making a beeline
to our sacred heart.
We are putting the call out
to deliver your hardest beats
to this man in black.
If you want the prize,
you must finish before sunrise.
This golden oldie,
and I do mean golden hit,
goes out to you, Mr. Wick.
And remember,
there is nowhere to run.
[POP SONG PLAYING ON RADIO]
[TIRES SCREECH]
DJ: I want to thank you all
for listening to WUXIA,
the place for
all your entertainment
and informational needs.
[IN SINGSONG] Good hunting.
[POP SONG CONTINUES
PLAYING ON RADIO]
And so it begins.
I'm going to need a gun.
I thought you'd never ask.
Nine-millimeter Pit Viper.
How'd you get this?
I know a guy who knows
a guy who shot a guy.
Twenty-one round
capacity magazine
with a built-in compensator
for virtually no muzzle flip.
Fiber-optic front sight,
ambidextrous safeties,
flared magwell
for faster reloads,
two-pound extreme trigger,
and for those more,
how shall we say,
intimate encounters,
this Viper has
ferocious fucking fangs.
[GUN CLICKS]
How close can you
get me to the church?
Amen.
Here we are,
gentlemen. [EXHALES]
Your ride.
[ENGINE WHIRRING]
WINSTON: When I advised you
not to dip your pinky
back into this pond,
I didn't think I'd get wet.
It'll all be over after today.
When I was burying Charon,
I was torn about what to
put on his gravestone.
A few words to sum
up an entire life?
Long live the king!
Had mine made years ago.
Modest.
[LAUGHS] Prophetic.
What did you decide?
Friend.
That's what he was
above all else.
A friend.
Au revoir et bonne
chasse, Monsieur Wick.
Thank you, King.
Jonathan.
Winston.
WINSTON:
Sunrise is at 6:03.
Don't be late for
all our sakes, hmm?
"Loving husband."
Hmm?
That's what I want on mine.
"John. Loving husband."
[PHONE RINGING]
[MAN ON PHONE
SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
Confirmed.
DJ: Good news, boppers.
We have a sighting.
Our man in black
has been spotted
in the Septième Arrondissement.
I think it's high time
we paint him red.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR HORN BLARES]
[CAR HORN BEEPING]
[GRUNTING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GROANING]
[GASPS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[TIRES SQUEAL]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MEN YELLING]
[ENGINE ROARS]
[ENGINE REVS]
[ENGINE REVVING]
It seems like our friends at
the guild dropped the ball,
and now it's rolling
to the Arc de Triomphe.
Let's see who picks it up.
[CAR HORN BLARING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[CAR HORN BLARING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[GRUNTS]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[TIRES SQUEALING]
[GROANING]
[CRASHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[GRUNTS]
DJ: Come on now, people.
We're gonna have
to do a lot better.
[POP SONG PLAYING ON RADIO]
Now, who's gonna be
our big winner?
[MEN SPEAKING FRENCH]
[CAR HORNS BLARE]
[GRUNTING]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[GRUNTS]
[CAR HORN BLARING]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[CAR HORN BLARES]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[JOHN GASPS]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GRUNTS]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Who is this?
You know, the question
you should be asking,
huh, is how much?
I think we have
the situation under control.
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[GUNSHOTS]
Because the way I see it,
is that if Mr. Johnny Boy
makes it to the church on time,
this could be your
last night as Marquis.
[CALL DISCONNECTS]
[BUS HORN BLARES]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[GUNSHOT]
[COCKS GUN]
[GUNSHOTS]
[DOG BARKING]
[DOG GROWLING]
[SHOUTS IN SPANISH]
[DOG YELPS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[BARKING]
[CAR HORNS BLARING]
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
DJ: A little traffic update.
I'm hearing the boys in black
couldn't get it done.
Our wicked friend
is on the move again.
He's headed your way,
my listeners of the 8th.
[ENGINE SPLUTTERING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[SPEAKING FRENCH]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[DOG GROWLING]
[BARKS]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[DOG SNARLING]
[GUNSHOT]
[BONES CRACK]
[PANTING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
[MUFFLED GUNSHOTS]
Yes?
Fine. You have a deal.
All right. 35 it is.
[CHUCKLES]
That wasn't our deal.
[GUNSHOTS]
Well, that's the only deal
being offered today.
[HANGS UP]
[CHUCKLES, GRUNTS]
Get him!
[DOG BARKS]
[GROWLING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN SCREAMING]
Phone!
[MAN GROANING]
[DOG SNARLING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
What? Now, you listen to me.
Forty.
You pay for the service.
[IN FRENCH]
DJ: Good news, boppers.
The lottery just went up.
[MEN SPEAKING HURRIEDLY]
[MAN SHOUTS IN FRENCH]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[MEN SHOUTING IN FRENCH]
[MEN SPEAKING FRENCH]
[UPBEAT ELECTRONIC
MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEN GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[MEN SCREAMING]
[MUFFLED GUNFIRE]
[MAN SHOUTS IN FRENCH]
[DOG BARKING]
[MAN SCREAMING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[JOHN GROANS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[TRACKER GROANS]
[CHOKING]
[DOG BARKS]
[GRUNTS]
[DOG SNARLING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[DOG YELPS]
[BARKING]
[SCREAMS]
[MEN SHOUTING IN DISTANCE]
[GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BULLETS RICOCHETING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
DJ: To all you boppers
still sitting on the side,
Mr. Wick has
the church in sight.
We are almost out of time.
Last chance to win the prize
before Mr. Wick's last sunrise.
So who out there is going
to climb those 222 steps?
[IN FRENCH]
[PANTING]
[TICKING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[MEN GRUNTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[SCREAMS]
[SILENCED GUNSHOTS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES IN DISTANCE]
[SMACKS LIPS]
[MAN SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY]
[GUNSHOTS]
[MAN GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[GUN CLICKS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[JOHN GROANING]
[CLANKS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
It appears Mr. Wick
won't be joining us.
[BELL TOLLING IN DISTANCE]
[GROANS]
[SOFT TAPPING]
CAINE: John?
John?
Caine.
What time is sunrise?
[GROANS]
Two...
maybe three minutes.
I need you to get to the top
of those stairs, John.
[SIGHS]
Yeah.
Ready?
[CANE CLANKS]
[GUN COCKING]
Twelve or nine?
Nine.
[MEN GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Six upstairs. Thanks.
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES IN DISTANCE]
[SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[COCKS GUN]
[DOG WHINING SOFTLY]
Ciao, ciao, Mr. Wick.
[GUNSHOT]
You can't shoot me.
[SIGHS]
Yeah, you're right.
But I can shoot him.
[CHOKING]
But I can hit you,
motherfucker. [SPITS]
Let's go, John.
[CANE CLANKING]
[GROANING]
[DOG GROWLING]
[IN SPANISH]
[GROWLING]
Nuts.
[SNARLING]
[GROANING]
You hit my puppy.
[GUNSHOT]
[TRACKER CLICKS TONGUE]
You know, you owe me.
Yeah.
[GRUNTS]
Nothing personal, John.
We're even now.
CAINE: Yeah.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SIGHS]
And so we begin.
We seek the truth and will
endure the consequences.
ALL: Consequences.
[BULLETS CLATTERING]
Go on now. Come on.
[GUN COCKS]
Positions, gentlemen.
See you
in the next life, brother.
Thirty paces.
Remember your daughter.
Fuck off!
What a beautiful sunrise.
Last words, Winston?
Just have fun out there.
[SIGHS]
Are you ready, Mr. Caine?
Mr. Wick?
[IN LATIN]
[IN ENGLISH] Fire!
[GUNSHOT ECHOES]
[GRUNTS]
Twenty paces!
Fire!
[WINCES]
[GROANS]
Nice.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Ten paces!
[GROANS]
Just kill him.
Those who cling to death,
live.
Those who cling to life,
die.
Fire!
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[EXHALES]
[DOG WHINES SOFTLY]
[IN FRENCH]
[IN ENGLISH]
As your sponsor,
I claim the coup de grâce.
Your weapon, give it to me.
Is my daughter free now?
Oui. You
and your daughter.
Enjoy.
Rules.
WINSTON: Ha.
You arrogant asshole,
he didn't shoot.
Consequences.
[PANTING]
[LAUGHS]
That's fucking good.
[JOHN GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Hmm.
Your obligation to The Table...
is satisfied, John Wick.
You are free.
As are you
and your daughter, sir.
You will be fully
reinstated, Mr. Manager.
All of your terms
will be fulfilled.
Our business here now
is concluded.
Good day.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
[JOHN GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
My brother.
You owe me one.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Yeah.
[CAINE WALKS AWAY]
Winston.
Jonathan.
Will you take me home?
Of course.
[JOHN BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Helen.
Never thought I'd see the day.
Where do you think he is,
heaven or hell?
Who knows?
[BOWERY KING CHUCKLES]
[IN RUSSIAN]
♪ You've taken everything
I love from me ♪
♪ Now it's time
To pay the price ♪
♪ Well, I'll be walking free ♪
♪ I'm gonna make it right
I won't apologize ♪
♪ No tears left to cry
I'm seeing Wick tonight ♪
♪ An eye for an eye
A life for a life ♪
♪ I'll see you in hell
On the other side ♪
♪ An eye for an eye
A life for a life ♪
♪ I'll see you in hell
On the other, other side ♪
♪ I'll try to burn for you ♪
♪ I'll meet you
In the afterlife ♪
♪ I'll take an eye for an eye
A life for a life ♪
♪ I'll see you in hell
On the other side ♪
♪ Bring you to your knees
Better pray I leave ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ I'll see you in hell
On the other side ♪
[THEME SONG PLAYING]
[VIOLIN MUSIC PLAYING]
[POCKET KNIFE CLANGS]